Some will fall. Some will fly.
Snow Angels is a drama, romance, crime film directed by David Gordon Green.
Waitress Annie has separated from her suicidal alcoholic husband, Glenn.
Glenn has become an evangelical Christian, but his erratic attempts
at getting back into Annie's life have alarmed her.
High school student Arthur works at Annie's restaurant, growing
closer to a new kid in town, Lila, after class.
When Glenn and Annie's daughter go missing, the whole town searches
for her, as he increasingly spirals out of control.
Annie Marchand, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Glenn Marchand, played by Sam Rockwell.
Arthur Parkinson, played by Michael Angarano.
Louise Parkinson, played by Jeannetta Arnette.
Don Parkinson, played by Griffin Dunne.
Nate Petite, played by Nicky Katt.
Snow Angels is a 2007 American drama film written and directed by David Gordon Green, based
on Stewart O'Nan's 1994 novel, and starring Sam Rockwell and Kate Beckinsale.
The film is centered on several characters dealing
with loss of innocence in a small town.
It premiered in the dramatic competition at the 2007 Sundance Film Festival, and was
released in the United States on March 7, 2008, by Warner Independent Pictures.
The film explores themes of depression, small town,
suicide, family relationships, young love.
The tone is emotional.